{
    "subject": "resource/Operation_Infatuate",
    "predicate": "ontology/place",
    "object": "resource/Walcheren",
    "human_readable": "Operation Infatuate took place in Walcheren.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8478981852531433,
            "question": "What was the name of the operation that took place in Walcheren?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459084987640381,
            "question": "Where did Operation Infatuate occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7040127515792847,
            "question": "When did Operation Infatuate take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6248507499694824,
            "question": "Was Operation Infatuate a military operation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5358853340148926,
            "question": "Who were the parties involved in Operation Infatuate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45518380403518677,
            "question": "What were the consequences of Operation Infatuate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4551202952861786,
            "question": "Was Operation Infatuate a success or failure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4531705677509308,
            "question": "What is the significance of Walcheren in relation to this operation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3585306406021118,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about Operation Infatuate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.291091650724411,
            "question": "What is known about the goals of Operation Infatuate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Operation Infatuate took place in Walcheren.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3875_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records about Operation Infatuate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3875_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Walcheren in relation to this operation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3875_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Operation Infatuate a success or failure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3875_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3875_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly mention that Operation Infatuate took place on Walcheren Island, providing evidence to support the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}